collegehoopsnet.com 2015-03-24

# Collegehoopsnet.com - Privacy Policy

COLLEGEHOOPSNET.COM (CHN) PRIVACY POLICY

CHN is committed to protecting your privacy. CHN collects no personal information about who visits our site. CHN uses a traffic service that shows information such as which internet service visitors are using, their screen resolutions, browser types, etc. but in no way does this reveal the name, email address, or any specific information whatsoever about the site's visitors. 

Demographic data: 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [ click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

We can see hostnames of our visitors through out 3rd party statistics provider (Webalizer). In other words, if you are in New York and you use earthlink, we may see that this person visited our site: 833.235.new-york.earthlink.net - but in no way does that tell us who you are. Other information we may see includes what we stated above \- screen resolution, browser type, domains, countries, etc., but we repeat - in no way does this identify any sort of personal information about you. We do not know who you are unless you tell us. 

Will CHN disclose the information it collects? 

CHN may eventually disclose the aforementioned GENERAL information about visitors (how many visitors, what countries are they from, etc)- information that does NOT identify who you are. We may disclose answers to questions such aa style= height= color=Arials: During what time periods do we receive the most visitors, what is the most common browser version of our visitors, what are the most popular internet services our visitors use, etc. 

About Our Advertisers and Affiliates: 

CHN works with third parties that serves ads to this site, these include BurstMedia and FastClick.. To find out more about how BurstMedia  and FastClick manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to burstmedia.com and fastclick.com.

CHN also works with TeamFanShop to provide affiliate sales.  Please visit TeamFanShop.com to view their privacy information.  CHN is not responsible for the privacy policies of it's affiliates or advertising partners.

Your consent: 

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Collegehoopsnet.com. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. But, now and forever we put your privacy first before any other concerns. We will never sell lists of email addresses from this site. We respect the privacy of our visitors.

Questions

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at collegehoopsnet@aol.com
